Prologue: Latifa’s Secret Diary

Today, on a whim, I decided to start a diary.

Almost two years have passed since Onii-chan left the village; I’ve studied a lot in that time, learned a lot of difficult words, and can now write sentences properly. That’s why I wanted to write down all of the fun things that have happened in the village every day, so that Onii-chan can read it, too. That way, we’ll be able to talk about everything that’s happened together.

While I’m at it, I’d be super happy if Onii-chan praised me for studying so hard, too.

Ehehe, just imagining it makes me happy already.

And so, I’d like to start my diary right away by writing about what happened today.

Today was a wonderful, clear, autumn day. It was a tiny bit chilly, possibly because winter was approaching, but being in the warm rays of sunlight felt very nice. As I was talking to Vera and Arslan, I thought about how fun it would be to go for a walk with Onii-chan on a day like this.

But that aside, now that I’m writing a diary and consciously thinking about it, I realized there are so many fun and happy things happening around me.

Sara, Orphia, Alma, Vera, Arslan, Uzuma, Granny Ursula, Mr. Syldora, Mr. Dominic... I’m with so many kind people every day, and I’m able to talk about so many fun things with them.

Yes, I am a very lucky person — and it’s all thanks to Onii-chan.

Onii-chan saved me from that pitch-black darkness. Without Onii-chan, I wouldn’t be here right now.

I’m so grateful for Onii-chan, I can barely look him in the eye.

But, right now, Onii-chan is on a journey outside of the village. He’s looking for his mom and dad — of this world — in a faraway place called the Yagumo region.

To be honest, not having Onii-chan beside me is a little lonely, but I understand. I know exactly how precious Onii-chan’s memories of his late mother must be.

I don’t have a lot of memories of my mom here, but even so, I can faintly remember being gently embraced in her arms many times. When I imagine my previous self in Onii-chan’s current place, I feel very sad.

That’s why... How should I put this? I can’t really express myself well, but I think... I can understand how Onii-chan must be feeling. It’s lonely, but I must endure it.

Anyway, Onii-chan and I are tied together by a miracle of fate, because my previous self has met the previous Onii-chan before, too. That’s why, no matter how far apart we are, I believe our hearts are strongly linked. Onii-chan even told me lots of stories I didn’t know about his previous self, before he left the village.

In this vast world, the only one who knows about the previous Onii-chan is me... No one else. When I think of it that way, it makes me wonder if I’m actually a very special person to Onii-chan.

Ehehe.

However, the previous Onii-chan had family and an extremely precious person to him, so I don’t know if I’m as special as that person... It makes me wonder sometimes.

Even so, I can’t let myself be discouraged! I’ll surely become someone special to him!

That’s what I’ve decided... because I love him. Both the present Onii-chan, and the previous Onii-chan.

That’s why I’ll become someone who can stand proudly, even if those precious people of Onii-chan’s were to appear before me, as the current Onii-chan’s little sister! Ehem!

So, I was writing whatever came to mind just now, but keeping a diary might actually be pretty fun! All of those memories of Onii-chan resurfaced, and my brush kept moving steadily across the page.

Ah, but now I want to see Onii-chan again. What should I do...

Wait, huh...? I just read over my writing... Isn’t this more like I’m writing a love letter of my feelings for Onii-chan, rather than a diary? Now I’m going to be too embarrassed to show anyone else...

No, no... Well, I didn’t intend on showing anyone in the first place... As for Onii-chan... It’ll be fine if I just read it out loud to him, right?

Yeah, that’s right! I’ll write more diary-like entries starting tomorrow. Ehehe.

Okay, time for the closing words.

I hope Onii-chan comes back soon!

— Diary, Day 1.

Chapter 1: Homecoming

Year 999 of the Holy Era. Late fall.

At the village of the spirit folk, just before the sun was to set...

In a room at the residence of the werefox Ursula, who was one of the three head elders of the village, Latifa finished writing her diary and put her quill down with a satisfied nod.

This is good enough for the first day, I think.

She picked up the journal she had just written in and stared at it intently.

“...This really is too embarrassing to show anyone else. I wrote about so much... I’ll have to put it away so that no one else can find it,” she murmured as she stood up, then glanced around the room.

“All right... there.” After fitting her diary into the corner of the bookshelf, she beamed with an innocent smile.

◇◇◇

Meanwhile, at the same time, Rio was flying through the skies above the great forest, where the spirit folk lived.

Many layers of wide-range sorcery force field stretched around the village, but the most powerful barrier among them was composed of anti-detection sorcery that could only be infiltrated with a certain level of spirit arts training.

The anti-detection effect was considerably weaker against intruders approaching from the air, but the villagers were informed from the moment they entered the barrier’s range. Even Rio, who was flying closer through the sky, would probably be detected soon.

At last, Rio thought sentimentally as he looked upon the giant tree of Dryas, towering near the village.

Roughly two weeks had passed since Rio had departed from the Yagumo region; even though he could fly with spirit arts, it had been a long journey.

As Rio immersed himself deep in thought, a tingling sensation ran through his entire body. He had entered the barrier, meaning the village would undoubtedly be able to sense his presence as an outsider. With the village right before his eyes, it was only a matter of time before someone came flying out at him.

Rio halted in his flight and remained airborne.

I wonder if everyone’s doing well. Especially Latifa... He smiled at the nostalgic memories that surfaced.

He hadn’t seen her for nearly two years. Maybe she’ll be mad at me, he wondered to himself.

After several minutes of waiting, Rio spotted a group of people flying toward him from the direction of the village.

“That’s... Orphia’s Ariel.”

He enhanced his vision with spirit arts and strained his eyes to see. Ariel was the middle class spirit the high elf girl Orphia was contracted to. Several figures were riding on the back of the beautiful, giant bird that looked similar to an eagle, and there were more figures flying alongside it by themselves.

The group seemed to have locked onto Rio’s figure, as they were making their way straight toward him. Their figures gradually grew larger and clearer in Rio’s vision, until eventually —

“Onii-chan!”

A familiar voice could be heard — the voice of an innocent and adorable girl. The owner of said voice was waving enthusiastically at Rio. Despite the group being fully-armed, there was no trace of hostility in the air, so Rio was all smiles as he returned the enthusiastic wave.

Immediately after, Ariel accelerated dramatically and closed in on Rio ahead of the others. In no time at all, Ariel had closed the distance between them, before continuing to soar higher right in front of Rio. Rio followed the sight with his eyes, then caught sight of a single girl jumping down from Ariel’s back. Rio rose nearly reflexively and caught the girl with a hug.

“Oops...”

“Welcome home, Onii-chan!” The werefox girl — Latifa — shouted as she fit snugly into Rio’s arms.

“I’m home. Jumping down like that is dangerous, you know?” Rio warned her with a wry smile.

“It’s fine, because I knew Onii-chan would be sure to catch me,” Latifa said with a carefree smile.

Rio couldn’t help but soften his expression. Unable to conjure up any additional words of warning for her, he gently petted her head.

“Ehehe.” Latifa grinned bashfully and rubbed her head against Rio’s chest.

“You’ve grown bigger, Latifa.”

“Yup. Of course I have — I’m nearly thirteen years old now!”

“I see. I’m glad you’re doing well... and to see everyone else is still the same, too. It’s been a while... I’m home,” Rio said with a happy smile and turned to the other faces hovering in the air.

The silver werewolf Sara and dwarf Alma were seated on Ariel’s back as Orphia floated in the air beside them. Uzuma, the winged werebeast who served the village as a warrior, was also nearby.

“Long time no see, Lord Rio. I am most relieved to see you are well, and to see that you have bulked up a fair bit, too. Perhaps you are even stronger now?” Uzuma said cheerfully.

“He really has. Rio, you look a lot more mature now. And very cool!” Orphia nodded in agreement.

“Thank you very much, both of you. I’m in the middle of my growth spurt,” Rio said bashfully.

“Fufufu. Rio’s so adult-like now, it seems Sara and Alma are feeling a little shy,” Orphia said with a mischievous smile, looking toward Sara and Alma. The two girls had been looking at Rio in awe when the spotlight landed on them, making them both flinch.

“I-I’m not acting shy at all!” Sara objected in a fluster.

“Sara’s the only one shy here. I was only thinking about how the air around Rio had changed a lot.” Alma turned her face away and excused herself with feigned composure.

“T-There you go again, saying things like that. It’s so obvious you’re feeling embarrassed, too!” Sara retorted without a moment’s delay.

“Sara was the one captivated by the sight of Rio.”

“Waaah, Alma! Don’t say such weird things!”

Alma and Sara’s usual back and forth unfolded before the group, making Rio let out a small chuckle.

“...Hmph, why are you laughing, Rio?” Sara asked with an admonishing expression.

“It’s nothing. I was just thinking about how it really feels like I’ve come home. The two of you have both turned into mature young women. It’s wonderful,” Rio answered as though he was holding back his amusement.

“Uh... T-Thank you very much,” Sara said with a blush on her cheeks. However —

“...I haven’t changed much, though,” Alma replied with a pout on her lips.

“That’s not true. You look more mature now than before, and you’ve grown a little taller too, haven’t you?” Rio said with a smile, shaking his head.

“...Well, yes, a little,” Alma nodded gently with a happy smile.

“Hmph. That must be nice, you two. Being praised by Rio like that,” Orphia muttered, envious.

“You’ve become more beautiful as well, Orphia. You seem even more calm and composed than before,” Rio said, complimenting her with a faint smile.

In fact, Sara, Orphia, and Alma were all in the middle of their growth period, so they had matured a lot since he had seen them last.

“Ehehe, thank you very much,” Orphia said with a broad, happy smile.

Just then, Latifa tugged at Rio’s coat from where she was being carried, and turned her expectant gaze up to him.

“Latifa’s also much more like a mature woman,” Rio laughed in amusement.

“Yup!” Latifa replied with a smile that stretched from ear to ear.

◇◇◇

After their initial greetings, Rio was led by Sara and the others as they descended into the village square. A large number of village children, who were playing there, noticed the group sink down from the skies.

“Welcome home, Rio!” Sara’s little sister, the silver werewolf Vera, came bounding over energetically.

“Hi, Vera — I’m home. I see you’re as lively as ever.”

“That’s right! And I see you’re close to Latifa, as always! Good for you, Latifa. You got to meet up with your beloved brother again!” Vera said, looking at Latifa being carried bridal-style in Rio’s arms.

“Yup! Thank you, Vera!” Latifa thanked her as she clung to Rio. She had been sticking right by his side since earlier.

“Please allow me to give Rio a hug later. I wanted to see him again, too,” Vera pleaded and waved her tail around happily.

“Sure, we can hug Onii-chan together!” Latifa nodded readily.

“Thank you for always being friends with Latifa. You’ve grown bigger, too, Arslan.” Rio said with a smile, turning to the werelion boy Arslan who had followed after Vera and stood motionless to the side.

“R-Right. Long time no see, Rio,” Arslan replied somewhat shyly. He gave a small shrug of his shoulders.

“Rio’s the one who’s gotten bigger and bulkier. You look a lot more adult-like than before.” Vera’s beautiful, silver hair fluttered in the wind as she looked up at Rio in amazement.

“Thank you. Sara and the others said the same.” Rio chuckled and looked toward Sara. Her eyes met Rio’s eyes, and she looked away in embarrassment.

“Fufufu. It seems my sister is too shy to look at a grown-up Rio,” Vera said with a complacent smile.

“I-I’m just nervous!”

As Sara refuted Vera in a fluster, Rio averted his gaze with a strained smile. Sara glanced at his profile.

Ugh... It’s all because Alma said those things. He’d definitely find me strange for panicking like this, Sara thought to herself.

Indeed, she was nervous — Rio looked a lot more mature than before. He had a calm air about him when they had lived together previously, but there was still something innocent and fleeting about him back then. Now, she could feel a sharp and intimidating steadiness to him, making him seem strangely mature despite his young appearance.

His body had also become sturdier, his movements were as guarded as always, and there was no doubting the fact he had become stronger.

He must have grown mentally, too, so it was possible that his new disposition was seeping into the air around him.

With that thought, Sara came to her own conclusion. I’ll have to have Rio spar with me sometime soon. I need to show him he isn’t the only one who’s grown! she thought eagerly.

At some point, the children in the square had gathered around Rio.

“Welcome back, Rio!”

“You went outside the village, right? What was it like?”

“Did you grow taller, Rio?”

“Rio, souvenirs! Souvenirs!”

They were all speaking at once.

“Rio won’t be able to answer anything if you guys all ask so many questions at once. Be more considerate and wait your turn. Anyway, the sun’s about to set, so it’s almost time for you guys to go home,” Sara warned the little boys and girls of the village in the tone of an older sister.

“Eeeh, but we wanna talk more!”

“Where are you guys going, Sara?”

“We wanna go with you!” The children all wailed.

Instead of asking the strict Sara, the children were shrewd enough to persistently plead at the gentle Orphia and Alma, who was unexpectedly good at caring for children.

“Geez, we’re going to see the head elders! You’ll be scolded if you keep making a fuss. Orphia and Alma, you two need to stop spoiling them so much,” Sara said strongly, reprimanding them.

“Geh, there’ll be lots of adults!”

“Aww...”

“Let’s go home! Home time!”

The children finally backed down.

“Vera, Arslan, you two make sure the smaller kids make it home safely.”

“Okay, got it!”

“Sure, leave it to us, Sara.”

At Sara’s order, Vera and Arslan nodded.

“Shall we get going, then, Rio?”

Thus, Rio was led to the town hall where the head elders were waiting.

◇◇◇

That night, in the cafeteria of the town hall...

After Rio had greeted all of the elders and informed them of his return, the head elders held a small welcome party for him.

In attendance was Rio as the guest of honor, the three head elders — high elf Syldora, elder dwarf Dominic, and werefox Ursula — as well as Latifa and the three girls who used to live together with them: Sara, Orphia, and Alma.

“I must say, you’ve grown into quite the adult. I’ll check to see whether your equipment needs any adjustments, so pop by my place sometime tomorrow. Was there anything about the equipment that you were less than pleased about?” Dominic asked as he poured sake into his cup. “Thank you very much,” Rio thanked him brightly. “Its ease of use was of the highest quality, but if I had to pick something I was unhappy with... I’d say its high quality drew too much attention, perhaps?”

“Wahaha, that makes sense... I see, I see. That sounds about right.” Dominic laughed heartily.

“Lord Rio, I heard that you were able to fulfill the goal of your journey. If it is all right with you, would you share some stories of the Yagumo region? I’m sure the girls are interested in hearing about it, too,” Ursula said as she looked at Sara and the others.

“Sure, I wouldn’t mind,” Rio nodded agreeably, then started to recount his journey.

He told them about how he couldn’t find any clues about his parents in the first few months, how he wandered the Yagumo region endlessly, and how he walked through several hundred towns and villages until he finally met his grandmother and learned of his cousin, before beginning his life in their village.

When he told them of Yuba and Ruri’s existence, Latifa spoke up.

“So, Onii-chan had a granny and cousin...” Latifa murmured from where she sat beside Rio, listening with round eyes.

“When I told them I had an adopted sister, they said they wanted to meet you, too. But I didn’t tell them about this village, so I couldn’t bring them here to see you,” Rio told her gently.

“...I would’ve liked to see them, too, I think,” Latifa responded hesitantly.

“...Hmm. Well, if it was Lord Rio’s family, then it may be possible for a temporary stay to be permitted under certain circumstances. But the Yagumo region is far... Well, let’s set that aside for now,” Ursula said worriedly, a strange weight to her words. Syldora and Dominic also carried troubled expressions and strained smiles, while Latifa and the other girls tilted their heads in confusion. Rio reacted similarly, unable to comprehend the meaning behind Ursula’s words.

...I guess it’d be better to hide the fact mom was born as royalty. It might result in the topic of my past being dragged on forever, and it’s meant to be kept secret, anyway, Rio thought, detaching himself from the conversation to decide how much he could reveal to Ursula and the others; he didn’t want to cause the conversation to take a darker turn through a slip of the tongue.

“So, Rio, how long will you be staying here this time?” Syldora asked, changing the subject.

“At most, a few months. I’m thinking of leaving the village before winter begins, to head for the Strahl region,” Rio answered with a serious look, straightening himself.

“...Onii-chan, are you leaving again?” Latifa asked sadly, pouting with unhappiness.

“I’m sorry, Latifa. I’ll make sure to return a little earlier this time,” Rio apologized with a strained smile.

Latifa grabbed onto Rio’s sleeve unhappily and looked up at him. “...You promise?” she asked.

“Yeah, I promise.” Rio nodded his head firmly. The others watched their exchange with pleasant smiles on their faces.

“Lord Rio, was there anything you ran out of during your journey? We shall make preparations for you before you leave on your next trip, so do not hesitate to inform us,” Ursula suggested brightly.

“Thank you very much. I still have plenty of stock with me, but there was one thing I thought of on my journey... I would be grateful if you could lend me your knowledge,” Rio said, bringing up his request carefully.

“Hohoho, that is fine. Speak your mind,” Ursula agreed readily.

Rio explained the idea that he had come up with while he was in the Yagumo region. “I was actually thinking of building a house to stay in on my journey, one that could be carried around in the Time-Space Cache.”

“Oho, a portable house, you say? Now that’s an interesting thought.” Dominic immediately showed strong interest; his natural architectural instincts as a dwarf had probably been roused.

“A house to carry around... That would mean a house with no foundation would be more preferable, so that it could be placed easily. Is that correct?” Ursula asked.

“Yes. However, it would probably require the use of spirit arts to stabilize the ground every time it was set up. Well... That aspect shouldn’t be a problem for Rio, but...” Dominic mumbled to himself, placing a hand against his mouth.

“...Hum. Dominic won’t be paying attention for a while when he’s in this state. Lord Rio, leave the house idea to him and rest easy. I’m sure a good home will be constructed for you,” Syldora said with a wry smile.

“No, I was just hoping for some advice so that I could build it myself...”

“That’s impossible. Even if you began constructing it alone, the dwarves of the village would only swarm you out of interest. It would be best for you to leave the house to Dominic and focus on entertaining Latifa and the girls as much as possible. Isn’t that right, Latifa?” Ursula responded cheerfully to Rio’s bewilderment, prompting Latifa to speak.

“Yup, I wanna stay with Onii-chan the whole time he’s in the village!” Latifa hugged Rio’s arm and nodded energetically.

After that, it was decided that Rio’s home construction would be left to Dominic and the other dwarves. Rio gave Dominic a simple explanation of the facilities and rooms he had planned, before they wrapped up the day in high spirits.

◇◇◇

“Ehehe!”

The next day, Rio was walking around the village with Latifa and Vera hanging off each of his arms.

Their destination was the spirit shrine built at the foot of the village’s giant tree — they were going to greet the spirit of the giant tree, Dryas, and inform her of Rio’s return. It was a one hour walk to reach the giant tree from the village on foot, and while the tree was only a stone’s throw away by air, they decided to take the opportunity and go on a picnic along the way.

With a troubled expression, Rio let the two cheerful girls have their way. Then, as the three of them were merrily making their way on foot, Rio and the girls passed Anya, the werecat.

“Oh my, if it isn’t Rio. I see you’re making quite a display upon your return.”

She was several years older than Rio, but because her species had long lifespans that aged particularly slowly in their teenage years, she barely looked any different to when Rio last saw her two years ago.

“Ah, Anya! Good morning!” Latifa and Vera said together, greeting Anya cheerfully.

“Morning. Are the three of you going out to have fun?” Anya asked.

Vera took the initiative to answer first. “Not quite. We’re meeting with my sister and the others after this.”

“Oho, with Lady Sara. Which means Lady Orphia and Lady Alma will be there too. Isn’t that more flowers than you can hold, Rio?” Anya nodded in a show of great interest before grinning at Rio.

“...Long time no see, Anya. I was thinking of paying Lady Dryas a visit, now that I’ve returned to the village,” Rio said with a strained smile, ignoring Anya’s curious gaze.

“Fufufu, looks like you’ve grown a little. As your elder, I’m happy. Not to mention, you’ve become really handsome, too.” Anya nodded with satisfaction and beamed.

“Thank you very much. I see you’re still as beautiful as always, Anya,” Rio thanked her with a grin.

“Nya?!” Anya’s cat ears trembled in shock.

“Nya?” Latifa and Vera both tilted their heads in unison.

“Nya... W-What are you saying, all of a sudden? I’ve got my eye on you,” Anya said in a high-pitched voice; there was a faint blush to her cheeks.

“What’s the matter, Anya?”

“...It’s nothing, Vera. I was just a little surprised Rio tried to flatter me while I was off guard, calling me beautiful of all things. Sheesh, I guess that means it wasn’t your defensive power that grew while you were gone... Since you’re doing it half-naturally, it’s even more wicked. Good grief!” Anya feigned composure as she shook her head at Vera. She muttered the latter half weakly.

“...It wasn’t just flattery,” Rio said in confusion.

“It’s fine, just get going to the Great Dryas already. This blockhead. Don’t keep Lady Sara and the others waiting. I have things to do, so I’ll be going now.”

With a tired sigh, Anya waved her hand and took her leave. Then, Vera opened her mouth in wonder.

“Didn’t Anya seem a little strange?”

“Ahaha, maybe. But she’s right, we shouldn’t keep Sara and the others waiting, so let’s get going,” Latifa agreed with a faintly strained smile, before pulling Rio’s arm along. Then, they met up with the other girls, and headed toward the giant tree Dryas resided in together.

◇◇◇

The moment Rio and the girls stepped onto the spirit shrine estate, they saw Dryas, who had manifested before them.

“Oh, my. I was wondering who it was, but it looks like the whole gang’s here... Welcome, welcome. I see Rio’s here, too — back already?” Dryas greeted the respectfully quiet party in a friendly tone.

“Yes, I thought I’d drop by and say hello. Everyone made food, so let’s eat together,” Rio explained on behalf of the others.

“My, thank you for taking the trouble. There’s not much here, but I’ll gladly welcome you. Follow me.” Dryas welcomed them happily and directed them inside; Rio and the girls followed her.

Dryas glanced at Rio. “Judging by your current state, your spirit still seems to be asleep, but the presence is stronger than the last time we met. The day it awakens may be approaching... Did anything change while you were on your journey?” she asked as they walked.

“No, nothing in particular comes to mind...”

“I see. Well, come visit me again when it awakens. I’d like to hear its story, and there may be many things I call tell it, too.”

“I will. Thank you very much.”

As they exchanged words, they arrived at the spirit shrine.

It was a shrine constructed from stone, with a staircase that led directly to the front, where there was a hall reserved for ceremonies that could look over the entire shrine grounds. At the very back across from the hall entrance was an altar.

This time, Rio and the others didn’t step up into the hall, instead walking around it and through a door that led further into the building. The door was located directly underneath the hall.

“I had no idea there was such a place under here,” Rio said with widened eyes.

Before him was a living space filled with various pieces of furniture. It was roughly 200 square meters in size, with several rooms toward the back.

“The people from the village made the interior. It doesn’t get used much, normally, but it’s useful when guests come over like this, or when the villagers sleep over in preparation for the Grand Spirit Festival.”

“I see.” Rio nodded in understanding.

It was basically a guest room. For the record, Dryas’ official dwelling was a cavern inside the giant tree, though she had never invited anyone there before.

“But, that aside, let us eat! Something smells great, what did you bring? I’m looking forward to it, fufufu,” Dryas said radiantly, looking over at the small packages they were carrying.

“Hehe, today we have the recipes and snacks Rio learned to make in the Yagumo region. I made a few things, too, so please try a little bit of everything,” Orphia said with a smile.

After that, the group unwrapped all of the food packages they had carried along and prepared for their meal. They sat down at the round table in the order of Rio, Latifa, Vera, Dryas, Sara, Orphia, and then Alma. Once they had all taken their seats and arranged the dishes on the table, they finally began to eat.

“My, the flavor in these vegetables is very rich. It’s delicious. And these steamed foods, too... The vegetable rice goes along with it perfectly.”

Dryas was all smiles as she elegantly filled her cheeks with food.

Spirits couldn’t starve to death, but they were able to refill their magic essence through eating food, to an extent. While there was no need for the food to be prepared in an extravagant manner, Dryas liked to eat homemade cooking, and was rather particular about the taste.

“The chicken with steamed vegetables is yummy. It’s full of flavor.” Vera stuffed her cheeks with rice as she picked up the steamed chicken.

“I like the taro.”

Latifa’s favorite appeared to be the taro with the steamed vegetables. Her small mouth broke out into a smile as she munched on the taro happily, fully enjoying the flavor.

“Hey, you two. You can’t just eat the things you like and nothing else,” Sara scolded with a tired expression.

“Okaaay!” Latifa and Vera gave their drawn-out reply together.

And so, just like that, time passed peacefully.

Once they finished eating, Orphia went to the kitchen and came back carrying tea. After taking the teapot from the tea cozy, she started pouring tea into the cups. The wafting scent of the tea made Rio and the others smile broadly.

“Ehehe, dessert, dessert.”

“It’s dessert time!”

Latifa and Vera were happily humming away as they sniffed at the variety of tea cakes that were placed on the table.

“Go ahead, before it cools,” Orphia said brightly after she finished pouring tea for everyone.

“I’ll do just that, then. Mm, it’s delicious!”

Dryas smelled the fragrance of the tea with a pleased expression before bringing the cup to her mouth. She grinned widely with happiness when the flavor of the tea spread in her mouth.

“Your tea etiquette is as wonderful as always,” Rio said, praising Orphia.

“Ehehe, thank you very much. I’d like to drink Rio’s tea sometime soon. Let’s have lots of tea parties again,” Orphia requested, grinning bashfully.

Rio nodded pleasantly. “Sure, I’d love to.”

With an embarrassed grin, Orphia peered at Rio’s face and asked once more to make sure. “Yay! That’s a promise, okay?”

Rio nodded and agreed, his smile growing all the larger. That was when Alma, who had been watching them from where she sat beside Rio, started to tug at his sleeve.

“Rio, what kind of snack is this bread? The dough is a little different to what I’m used to...” she asked as she looked up at his face.

“That snack is called a manju. It’s normally filled with a sweet paste made from red bean, but I tried to make them with whipped cream as well this time.”

“Red bean... and whipped cream? It looks delicious. May I try one?”

“Of course.” Alma hesitantly reached for a manju after Rio agreed.

“Then I’ll try one, too.”

“Me too.”

“And me!”

All the girls suddenly reached for the manju at once, and in no time at all, everyone had a manju in their hands.

“It’s so yummy! The texture’s springy and the red bean goes well with the whipped cream!”

As they all took bites of the manju, Vera spoke up with her opinion first. The others also widened their eyes at the sweetness that spread throughout their mouth.

“I’m glad you found the taste to your liking.” Rio’s lips turned up in a happy smile.

After that, they chatted noisily with each other as they enjoyed their tea and snacks. Time passed in the blink of an eye, and before long, it was time to wrap things up.

Chapter 5: Meeting Who In This World?

The refreshing morning sun cast its rays through a small skylight in the ceiling as Rio opened his eyes a bit, gradually waking up in his bed.

The custom-made bed crafted by Dominic, the elder dwarf, was big enough to fit several people on it, while still offering the greatest level of comfort possible.

Despite the unexpected turn of events that occurred yesterday, Rio had still been able to sleep soundly through the night and woke up feeling wonderfully rested.

That’s right... Miharu, Aki, and Masato are here. I have to make breakfast... Rio thought sleepily, moving his hand sluggishly to grab the blankets and peel them away.

...Hm?

His hand suddenly squeezed around something soft. It definitely wasn’t his blanket or bedcover, and it wasn’t the mattress, either; it had a strange elasticity and springiness to it.

It fit into the palm of his hand snugly, its warmth comforting. When Rio tried to move his hand to confirm the sensation, he could feel a wonderful response in his hands.

...What is it? Rio wondered, his mind still half-asleep. Thinking it was strange, he gently tried to move his hand once more.

“Mm...”

This time, he thought he heard the seductive sigh of a woman — and with it, the sound of rustling fabric too. Rio gently removed his hand from the soft sensation and, with his eyes fearfully fixed on the ceiling, peeled back the covers and peeked under the blanket.

“Zz... z...”

He heard the peaceful breathing of someone sleeping next to him. Cautiously, Rio turned his head to the side.

There was an unfamiliar girl sleeping soundly next to him. She looked to be in her mid-teens, just like Rio; she was a beautiful girl with long, peach-colored hair. No, an incredibly gorgeous beauty with long, peach-colored hair.

However, there was a kind of transparency to her existence, almost as if she wasn’t real; an evanescence that gave a mystical and artificial impression.

“Mmh...” The girl stirred restlessly underneath the covers, reaching out and grasping the sleeve of Rio’s pajamas, before drawing her face closer to him. Her breath blew gently against his ear.

Rio’s mind snapped awake, but he wasn’t able to think.

“...” He gazed at the face of the unfamiliar girl from point-blank range, then turned his eyes back to the ceiling and relaxed, sinking heavily into the mattress once more. He closed his eyes.

Is this a dream? I must still be asleep. Yes, that must be it, Rio thought to himself, trying to convince his own mind and avoid the reality of the current situation.

No matter how soundly he was asleep, he would have awakened the minute he detected the presence of an unknown person next to him. Not to mention the fact that the intruder detection barriers around the house would have activated first. This had to be a dream.

Rio’s thoughts churned rapidly until he came to the conclusion that it was a dream. Then, he squeezed his eyes shut tightly.

And yet, he still felt oddly awake.

After a minute or so had passed, Rio slowly opened his eyes and flipped back all of the covers in one single movement. There, a truly impossible sight spread before him: snow-white skin, extremely well-balanced limbs that were smooth and feminine, and two soft-looking mounds.

In other words, there was a completely naked peach-haired beauty before him.

“EEEEEEEEH?!” In his horror, Rio let out an incredulous yell. Never in either life had he ever experienced the act of waking up next to a naked woman sleeping beside him.

Woken up by Rio’s yelling, the woman sat up in the bed. With her legs folded underneath her, she stared at Rio in a daze. The series of movements she made was strangely erotic, making Rio avert his gaze without thinking.

W-Why am I sleeping with a naked girl?! Rio yelled in his head. His face was burning hot, yet his body had broken out in a cold sweat. If his eyes happened to wander even a bit, the girl’s bare body would come into his view. He tensed up.

“W-What’s the matter, Haruto?!” Miharu asked, boldly peering through the door of Rio’s bedroom.

Dominic had crafted the room to be perfectly soundproof, but Rio had chosen to leave his door open in order to hear things while asleep, which was why Rio’s shouts had reached the living room. Miharu had been trying to take the initiative after Rio accepted them into his care by getting up before anyone else and making breakfast.

“...Huh? Ah, umm, err...”

When Miharu spotted Rio and a naked girl sitting near each other on the oversized bed, she hesitated, flustered. She attempted to explain herself, but her cheeks were gradually reddening. Rio covered the girl’s body with a blanket in a hurry, but it was already too late — what she had just seen was already burned into Miharu’s mind. Unsure of what to do next, she found herself tearing up.

It was understandable — their gentle and sincere savior had brought over a naked and beautiful girl to spend the night while they were unawares, after all. From Rio’s point of view, that was in no way the truth, but the current situation couldn’t help but give off that impression.

“W-Wait, that’s not it! Mii — Miharu! This is a misunderstanding...” Rio tried to explain himself in a fluster, but he was at a loss for words. Even if he wanted to deny everything, he didn’t know how to explain it.

“Huh?!” The peach-haired girl tilted her head in question, watching Miharu steadily before suddenly clinging to Rio. The blanket that covered her fluttered up, making Rio’s body flinch, whereas Miharu’s face had also reached its peak in redness.

“I-I’m sorry! I shouldn’t have opened your door without warning... I didn’t see anything! B-Bye now! —Oww!” With great force, Miharu bowed her head, rotated 180 degrees, then made her immediate retreat. However, in her rush, she crashed straight into the door frame.

“A-Are you all right?!” Rio asked in a panic.

“I’m fine... Ugh... I’m sorry... forgive me. I’m so clumsy.” Miharu staggered as she repeatedly bobbed her head, face flushing red in embarrassment as she retreated successfully this time.

Only Rio and the stranger were left in the room. The urge to chase after Miharu surged within Rio, but he hung his head in disappointment instead.

“...Umm, who are you? Could you explain this situation to me?” he asked, then placed a blanket over the girl. He wasn’t about to leave her as she was, but he needed to sort out the situation at hand first.

“I’m the spirit contracted to Haruto,” she answered in a clear and beautiful voice, cocking her head curiously.

“Spirit... I see. The contract spirit. So you’re...” Rio calmed immediately at the girl’s answer.

Realizing who the girl was, he observed her face and found her to have a very divine look about her. However, she seemed almost artificial in a way, her beauty leaving a cold and fleeting impression. Her aura was similar to Dryas’s in the spirit folk village, though Dryas had a much greater range of emotions than the girl before him right now.

It made sense considering the situation, and the girl had that faint feeling of having a life force characteristic of spirits — Rio concluded that the girl in front of him really was his contract spirit.

“...There’s a lot that I want to ask you. Who are you? Why are you contracted to me? You were the one who gave me the directions to save Miharu and her friends, right?”

Rio asked question after question. He had to understand who his contract spirit was, and how much she knew. He had always wanted to find out, actually. However, the girl shook her head slowly in a troubled way.

“I don’t know,” she replied simply.

Rio’s face fell in disappointment. She had dodged his questions. “Y-You don’t know...? Didn’t you tell me to head southeast when I was in Amande? And you taught me how to use spirit arts, back when I was still a child... Wasn’t that you?” he asked, pulling himself together.

“I don’t know,” the girl answered with an emotionless expression, although her voice had a hint of sadness in its tone. She quietly extended her hand and gently grabbed Rio.

“Warm,” a soft murmur seemed to reach Rio’s ears as she clutched his hand. However, the girl’s mouth had not moved, and her expression looked rather relieved.

Rio was completely thrown off balance. “Umm, okay... Could you at least tell me your name?” he asked with a sigh.

“I don’t know my name, either,” the girl answered with a sad look in her eyes.

“Y-You don’t know your name? Err, then, what do you know?” Rio questioned, bewildered.

“I will stay by Haruto’s side, so I want a name,” she said.

“...By my side, huh.” Rio’s face fell with gloom.

The girl looked at Rio’s face a little uneasily. “Can I?”

“You... can, but why me?” Rio asked in return, confused.

“I exist for Haruto’s sake,” the girl said plainly, showing no sign of shame. Her words were almost like a graceful and pure confession, though the girl probably had no intention of coming off that way.

Rio’s eyes widened before a giggle escaped from his lips. “...Haha. Is that so?”

For some mysterious reason, he didn’t feel any hesitance in accepting the girl’s attitude. Was it because she was his contract spirit? He didn’t know for sure, but that was what Rio assumed.

“Then, I guess... it is what it is. We’ll have to think of a name for you.”

For now, Rio decided to accept the girl’s presence here.

The girl showed a fleeting smile as she nodded. “Yeah.”

“...Speaking of names, you know my name, right?” he asked, nearly feeling captivated by that smile. Now that he was mentally calming down, he realized the girl had been calling him Haruto.

“Because Haruto is Haruto.” The girl returned his question with a curious look. Perhaps it was spontaneous, but her words sounded profound.

Rio scratched his head with a troubled expression. “No... Well, yes, but that’s not quite... Do you know my other name?” he asked carefully.

“I know. Rio,” the girl responded without missing a beat.

“So you know that one, too. How much do you know about my past?” Rio placed a hand by his mouth in thought.

“I know everything there is to know about Haruto.” The answer that came back to him was rather unexpected, leaving Rio feeling taken aback.

“Everything... Which means, umm... Everything about Amakawa Haruto, too?”

“You mean the Haruto that came before the Haruto that exists now?” The girl’s response was rather philosophical, but it told Rio everything he wanted to know.

“...So, you know.”

Rio could almost feel a headache coming on. Just as he had decided to hide his previous life from Miharu, Aki, and Masato, someone who knew of his previous life had appeared. When he thought about it, he realized that this girl and his three Japanese guests couldn’t communicate with each other, so there shouldn’t be any issues.

“Don’t worry. I won’t tell them.” The girl shook her head slowly.

“That’s... Right, okay. Thank you.” Rio was almost about to ask something, but after a moment of hesitation, thanked her with a strained smile. It was a topic he wanted to avoid, but since she had brought it up first, it felt like he now owed her something.

He asked one last thing. “...And do you know why you know those things, by any chance?”

“I don’t know. Because I knew before?” She shook her head, remaining as expressionless as ever as she tilted her head in question.

Rio watched her quietly as she watched him back. In the end, Rio was the first one to avert his gaze — there was no telling how long they could have stared at each other.

“...About your name. Are you sure you want me to name you? It’s your name, so maybe it’d be better for you to think of one yourself,” Rio sighed.

“I want a name from Haruto,” the girl requested immediately.

“Erm, then... Can you give me some time to think about it?” Rio asked with a troubled look. It wasn’t easy to come up with a name on the spot, and he didn’t think names were something that should be decided so easily anyway.

“Okay.” She nodded.

Rio had asked everything he wanted to know for now, so he processed the situation in his head. For now, she doesn’t seem to be a bad person. Which means... what I need to do now is...

“I’d like to clear up the misunderstanding with Miharu right away, so could you come with me? Oh, but we’ll have to get you some clothes to wear first...”

Just as he thought to go talk to Miharu about the situation, he remembered the girl was completely naked under the blanket and paused, at a loss. The sensation of what he touched earlier and the beautiful body he caught a glance of resurfaced in his mind, making him shake his head furiously.

“Clothes... Like this?” The girl murmured quietly. A flash of light escaped from beneath the blanket before she lifted the covers.

“Wah! W-Wait! ...Huh?” Rio hurriedly averted his gaze from such a bold action, but the flash of a non-skin color in the corner of his eye made him glance back timidly. The girl was now wearing a simple dress.

“H-How?” Rio nearly found himself captivated by how cute she was, but his doubt won over her charm.

“I weaved it with ode and mana,” the girl replied nonchalantly.

“Right, so that light just now was spirit arts... No, wait. You can do that?” Rio questioned with a tilt of his head, nodding in half-understanding, half-residual doubt. He had never heard of clothes being crafted by ode and mana before. “Well, whatever. Let’s go. You... might not speak her language, but I’ll explain everything, so just stay next to me.” With a sigh, Rio stood up from the bed; how she had made her clothing wasn’t an issue at the moment. He felt completely exhausted, despite having just woken up.

“I can speak the language, though,” the girl offered nonchalantly. Until now, they had been conversing in the common Strahl tongue, but the language the girl had used just now was Japanese.

“So you can speak Japanese, too. Well, if you knew about my previous life, then... that makes sense?”

“I can speak all the languages that Haruto can speak.”

“...I see.” Rio was no longer surprised, now simply accepting the explanations as they came. “Let’s get going, then. You can leave the explanation to me, but it’d be helpful if you could speak up if Miharu asks you anything.”

“Okay,” she nodded, before getting up from Rio’s bed.

He then opened the door to his bedroom and headed toward the living room where Miharu was most likely to be, his footsteps heavy.

◇◇◇

Accompanied by his new guest, Rio finally stepped into the living room. Miharu seemed to be in the kitchen; she had noticed that Rio and the girl had left his bedroom, but she continued to focus on her cooking while hiding her embarrassment. Meanwhile, it seemed as though Aki and Masato were still asleep.

“Umm, good morning, Miharu.” Rio approached Miharu with determination, speaking in a voice that was louder than usual.

“G-G-Good morning, Haruto! Umm, I’m preparing breakfast right now, so... err, could you please wait a little longer?” Miharu blurted out, avoiding eye contact with Rio. Her cheeks were still stained scarlet and her panic was clearly visible.

Rio was too shaken to notice earlier, but her apron and uniformed figure were very domestic and homely. It was the epitome of sweetness, and Rio found himself enchanted before he knew it. “Umm, is it all right if we speak for a moment? It’s about her,” he said to Miharu with a glance at the spirit girl waiting behind him.

“Ah, yes. W-What is it?” Miharu asked, finally looking at the girl. Her earlier impression of the girl’s naked state had been so strong that she hadn’t noticed her beautifully-refined face. Her eyes widened in surprise.

For a moment, silence fell between them.

With a deep breath, Rio opened his mouth. “I know you must be surprised by the sudden turn of events, but I’d like to start by telling you the truth. There are higher lifeforms in this world called ‘spirits,’ and she is one of those spirits...” He knew he had to explain this part properly.

“A... spirit? Her?” Miharu looked at the girl questioningly. While Miharu knew what the word “spirit” meant, she couldn’t see the girl as anything other than a human in terms of appearance. She did have a beauty that was almost ethereal, though.

“...Miharu.” When the girl met Miharu’s eyes, she murmured her name.

Miharu was taken aback for a moment. “Ah, yes. I’m Ayase Miharu. Err, what’s your name?” she asked.

“I don’t have a name.” The girl shook her head sadly, then looked at Miharu as though envious over the fact that Miharu had a name.

“Oh... Y-You don’t have a name?” Miharu looked over at Rio in bewilderment.

“Yes. I don’t know if it’s because she’s a spirit... but she doesn’t have a name. I barely know anything about her as well, actually.”

“Huh? Ah, umm, is that... so.” Unable to process the flow of the conversation, Miharu tilted her head in confusion.

“Yes. She contracted herself to me while I was unaware, and had been sleeping within me this entire time — until just now. I’ve never met her face-to-face, nor spoken to her before. Then, this morning, she suddenly appeared outside of me and... umm, invaded my bed. I yelled because there was an unknown girl beside me when I woke up... I-I swear I didn’t do anything dirty to her!” Rio appealed to Miharu with everything he had, bowing his head vigorously.

“T-There’s no need for you to lower your head! I think I understand what you’re saying, somewhat! If anything, it was m-my fault I peeked inside your room without warning, so I’m the one who should be apologizing! I’m sorry!” Miharu apologized in return, gesturing wildly in a fluster to stop Rio.

“You... believe me?” Rio raised his head timidly and peered at Miharu’s face. To be honest, he wasn’t expecting her to believe him so easily, and had been prepared to be hated for being indecent.

Miharu straightened up and nodded firmly. “Y-Yes. I don’t think you’re the type of person to lie for no reason.” She smiled bashfully.

“T-Thank you very much...” Rio sighed in relief, the strength draining out of him.

“Okay now?” The spirit girl tilted her head and asked Rio.

“Yeah. Thanks.” Rio smiled happily.

“So, she can speak Japanese?” Miharu asked curiously, watching the girl’s face.

“Yes. She was born and grew up as a spirit in this world, but apparently she can speak any language I can speak, so...”

“S-Spirits must be amazing... And she’s really beautiful, too. Even though she doesn’t look any different to us humans on the outside, there is certainly something otherworldly about her aura,” Miharu said while staring at her in awe.

“Miharu is beautiful, too,” the girl suddenly said.

Miharu’s eyes rounded in surprise. “Huh? M-Me? That’s not true,” she denied.

“...No, I think you’re beautiful, too, Miharu,” Rio interjected hesitantly.

“Ah, oh, H-Haruto, not you too. ...Ah, t-that’s right! I have to make breakfast!” Unsure of how to respond, Miharu blushed furiously and fled to the kitchen in a hurry.

“Oh, Haruto. Morning...” A sleepy Masato appeared in the living room, but the instant he saw the spirit girl next to Rio in his vision, he froze on the spot in shock.

“Good morning, Masato,” Rio said with a wry smile. However, Masato was still frozen on the spot, his breath taken away by the appearance of the girl.

“...”

“Oi, Masato. What are you standing around for? You’re blocking the way... Geez!” Aki was awake, now. When she grew impatient of Masato blocking her way, she squeezed past him and into the living room since he showed no signs of moving.

“Ah, good morning, Haru...to.” Aki tried to greet Rio politely when she spotted him inside the living room, but she froze just like Masato had when she saw the spirit girl next to him.

Chapter 7: Preparing To Move

A month and a half passed since the shopping trip in Amande. During that time, Miharu, Aki, and Masato had remained shut away inside the rock house, cramming the common tongue of the Strahl region into their heads. Since nothing could proceed if they weren’t able to speak the language, they prioritized learning the language over everything else, beating words and phrases into their heads from morning to night, even during meals.

While there is plenty to be said about the number of hours needed to acquire a foreign language to a conversational standard, Rio’s Japanese guests were able to study the Strahl common tongue for over 400 hours over the span of a month and a half — that culminated to nine hours a day on average. That number became much higher once their own voluntary self-study time during breaks was included.

In the beginning, a lot of the time was spent explaining the grammar structures in Japanese, but as time passed, more emphasis was placed on conversation. The lessons proved to be successful, as the three were able to converse to an optimal degree. As the eldest, Miharu showed the most remarkable improvement — as long as her conversation partner spoke slowly, she was able to reply with halting speech.

On one morning after a month and a half had passed, Rio and Miharu were cooking breakfast in the kitchen and speaking to each other using what Miharu had learned.

“Haruto... can you give... frypan?” she asked Rio in a clumsy Strahl tongue.

“Sure, here you go.”

“Thank you very much. Bacon egg or fried egg... Which do you want today?”

Rio thought for a moment before making his request with a faint smile. “...Let’s see. I want to eat a fried egg today.”

“Understood. Leave it... to me.” Miharu picked up the frying pan and pumped her fists in a cute gesture.

“You can say quite a few things now.”

“It’s all thanks... to Haruto.”

“It’s because you worked hard, Miharu.”

“No... it’s because... you were teaching... constantly.”

“Since the three of you have learned quite a few words at this point, I’m thinking it’s about time we moved from this field.”

“Moved...?”

“Yes,” Rio interrupted, speaking in Japanese. “This conversation is about to get complicated, so I’ll use Japanese now. Staying here like this makes it hard to move around, and that’s ineffective for gathering more information about your friends. There are some trustworthy people I know that we may be able to rely on, but I’ll need to ask them first. The probability is low, but there’s even a chance these people may know something about you guys.”

“I see...”

“If possible, I’d like to ask those people to look after you while I finish some personal errands of my own and gather information. What do you think?”

“Umm... I’m sure you have your own life to concern yourself with, so it’s okay if you put us second. We’ll let you decide what you need to do,” Miharu said apologetically, bowing her head to Rio.

“All right. Then we’ll move closer to Amande today. I’ll have you guys wait there while I pay a visit to my acquaintances. It’ll take roughly two weeks for me to return, so I’ll leave Aishia behind to protect you, and if you need anything during that time you can feel free to go shopping in Amande, too,” Rio said with a slight smile.

He wasn’t shameless enough to suddenly bring Miharu and the others along to the spirit folk village and just leave them there for the spirit folk to look after. The spirit folk had already cut off contact with the outside world, so it was possible that they would refuse, but he would go through all the proper steps to make the request.

“I’m sorry for making you have to consider every little thing. As you’ve been looking after us, I won’t say that we’ll be fine... but I’m sure we’ll somehow manage ourselves, especially with Ai-chan here. So... you can leave the house to us.”

“Okay, thank you.” Rio nodded amicably in an effort to avoid making Miharu worry any more than she already was.

Afterward, they had their breakfast, then moved the house to the middle of a forest on the outskirts of Amande. There had been rumors of people going missing along the western road the last time Rio had gathered information in Amande, so he set up the house near the east side of the city instead.

◇◇◇

The next morning, Rio dressed himself in his Black Wyvern armor and prepared to leave. “All right then, Aishia — I’m leaving everyone to you,” he said in the living room.

Aishia nodded quietly. “Sure.”

While she looked like a fragile young woman, Aishia was actually a humanoid spirit ranked high-class or greater. Since she could use the same level of spirit arts as Rio, there was no one better for the role of a bodyguard.

“I’m going to leave this spirit stone filled with essence with you while I’m gone, so you can use this to replenish your magic essence if anything happens,” Rio said, handing Aishia a pebble-sized emerald green spirit stone that glowed. It was possible to store an enormous amount of essence in a green spirit stone, even one of this size. The Time-Space Cache Rio received from the spirit folk used a stone of a similar size, too.

“...Understood. I tied a temporary path to Miharu just in case, so it’ll be okay,” Aishia said, taking the spirit stone.

“With Miharu... Really?” Rio’s eyes widened, and he looked at Miharu.

“Yes. Apparently, we have quite a large amount of magic essence within us? I don’t really get it, but I told Ai-chan she could use whatever she needed.” Miharu didn’t seem to fully understand it all yet, but nodded firmly anyway.

“...I see. I’m relieved, then.” Rio was interested in how the three of them had a large amount of essence, too, but was glad that that was the case so he didn’t have to worry as much about them.

“Please go safely, Haruto,” Miharu said.

“Yes. You don’t have to see me off from here,” he replied.

“Have a safe trip, Haruto.”

“See you later, Haruto.” Aki and Masato offered their words of parting to Rio as well.

“Thanks. Make sure you two listen to Miharu and Aishia.”

“Ahaha, we know.”

“That’s right! We’re not kids anymore!”

Aki and Masato nodded with strained smiles.

“You’re still a brat, though,” Aki noted.

“And there’s only one year difference between us,” Masato retorted, starting their usual bickering.

Rio watched Aki and Masato get up to their usual antics with a smile. “Looks like you’ll be all right to me. I’ll be going, now,” he said, and turned on his heel. He was relieved to see the youngest of the three showing no signs of worry.

Rio opened the front door and waved back at Miharu and the others, who were waving with all their might. Finally, he looked at Aishia with an entrusting smile, before the door shut.

“The three of you need to study until Haruto returns,” Aishia said.

“Ugh, so we’re doing the same old thing even with Haruto out.” Masato hung his head gloomily.

“We don’t have a choice. If we can’t speak the language, it’s too dangerous to even go outside. You’re the most behind, so work harder,” Aki said with an exasperated expression.

“Fufu. Let’s show Haruto how much we’ve improved when he comes back,” Miharu said with a smile.

◇◇◇

Once Rio stepped outside, he spoke the activation spell to use the Time-Space Cache on his left wrist.

“Dissolvo.”

The air above his hand warped, and a jade green spirit stone appeared. While it was the same color as the Time-Space Cache, its size was larger than the other spirit stone.

“Transilio.”

Rio activated the spirit stone in his hand — the teleportation crystal. The air around Rio and the teleportation crystal instantly started to distort in an exaggerated way, and in the next moment, Rio disappeared. The view in front of Rio’s eyes changed immediately, too.

“Looks like I made it back safely,” Rio murmured to himself.

Gentle rays of sunlight filtered through the trees of the forest scenery spread before him. It was his first time actually using the teleportation crystal, so he was surprised at how the scenery had changed in an instant. Thankfully, it seemed as though he had been able to teleport to the correct coordinates.

The crystal changed from green to turquoise; as the amount of magic essence inside a spirit stone increased, the color changed from colorless to blue. As it continued to increase, the colors changed to turquoise, leaf green, then finally jade green — so quite a large amount of essence was used.

I don’t think I should be that far from the village, but where is this exactly?

Rio put the teleport crystal away into his pocket and smiled at the vaguely familiar scenery. Then, he kicked off from the ground and rose into the air to check his current location, breaking through the canopy and into the skies above the forest.

I’m outside of the residential area... but pretty close to the village — about one or two minutes away by flight. At this distance, they may have detected the distortion in essence from the teleportation sorcery I used.

Someone may have set out to get him already. With that in mind, Rio began to fly toward the residential district visible in the distance at a leisurely pace.

Sure enough, a group of people were waiting in the skies above the village. There were several warriors of the village, with Orphia among them.

“See, it is Rio after all! You came back fairly quickly this time,” she said with a happy smile as she approached.

“Hello, Orphia. I have a little news this time... and a request,” he said somewhat apologetically.

“I see... Then we should hurry to the elders immediately. Follow me — it’s this way.”

Orphia seemed to sense that Rio had an important matter to discuss and began to lead him away without asking any further questions. The villagers around them followed.

“Thank you very much. The truth is... my contract spirit woke up,” Rio said as he flew alongside Orphia.

“Eh, really?!” Orphia asked with widened eyes.

The spirit sleeping within Rio had been a humanoid spirit, after all. To Orphia, who held spirits in high regard, the awakening of Rio’s spirit was a big deal.

“Yes. Due to certain circumstances, she isn’t present right now, but I’ll discuss more about that — as well as my request — with the elders.”

Orphia nodded. “I see... I’m sure everyone will be shocked. Let’s hurry over!” She watched Rio’s expression carefully before raising her flight speed by a small amount.

◇◇◇

Rio and the others landed before the giant tree house that was used as the town hall of the village. Latifa was waiting there, along with Sara, the silver werewolf, and Alma, the elder dwarf.

“Latifa... Sara and Alma too...” Rio’s eyes widened when he spotted the girls.

“Ehehe. There was a big pulse of mana, so everyone was excited that Onii-chan might have come back. We saw Onii-chan flying in the air and hurried here,” Latifa explained proudly. She must have run, as she was still out of breath.

“The two of them were in such a hurry — it was a huge pain,” Alma interjected with a wry smile.

“Y-You’re the one who decided to come along, Alma,” Sara added on in embarrassment. Orphia smiled.

“Fufu, so the two of you both wanted to see Rio again as quickly as possible.”

“Mrgh...” Sara and Alma groaned in embarrassment, but their lack of denial implied it was the truth.

“Onii-chan, you came back quickly this time.” Latifa beamed a smile full of purity and innocence.

“Yeah. My contract spirit woke up, and I have a lot of other things I wanted to discuss,” Rio answered with a faintly strained smile.

“Y-Your spirit has awoken?!” Sara and Alma were both taken aback.

“Yes. She’s not here right now, but I’ll bring her along next time.”

“In that case, we have to hurry to the head elders quickly. They should be upstairs,” Sara urged, and the group stepped into the town hall.

◇◇◇

Roughly half an hour later, in the meeting room on the top floor of the hall, Rio faced the council of elders that had assembled on short notice. Latifa and the other girls remained gathered in a corner of the room.

“So, is it true? Lord Rio’s contract spirit has awoken?” Syldora, the high elf seated in the middle of the three head elders, asked.

“Yes. She woke up just a month and a half ago.”

“...A month and a half ago would be the same time as when that vast torrent of ode and mana surged from the direction of the Strahl region,” Syldora surmised with a contemplative look. The pillars of light hadn’t been visible from the position of the village, but the aftermath of the ode and mana torrent was something that they clearly detected.

“So the waves reached here as well,” Rio said with a wry smile.

“Was that surge possibly related to your contract spirit’s awakening, Lord Rio?” asked the werefox head elder Ursula.

“No... I am not sure. However, the surge of ode and mana that everyone felt was most likely created via the sorcery of the six pillars of light.”

“...Do continue,” Ursula pressed.

“I believe the true form of those six pillars of light to be a type of time-space sorcery... something that can summon humans from other worlds into this one. There are religions in the Strahl region that believe in the deities called the Six Wise Gods. According to their ancient texts, it is said that six heroes who played an active role in the Divine War will return once more alongside six pillars of light. That is why the rumor of the heroes returning is spreading throughout Strahl like wildfire.”

“Heroes... you say?” The elders in the room burst into a commotion after hearing it was possible that heroes from the Divine War had returned.

Rio glanced over at Latifa; her eyes were round as she carefully watched him. Like Rio, she also had memories of a life in another world. She must have been curious as to whether the other world involved was Earth.

I’ll explain everything to Latifa later, Rio thought to himself with a strained smile.

“Does everyone know of the tales of the heroes passed down within the Strahl region?” he asked the elders sitting across from him.

“Even us spirit folk retain records of the Divine War that unfolded over a thousand years ago. It affected our ancestors, who lived toward the center of the continent, after all. It is said that they fought to drive away the evil forces,” Syldora replied.

“In order to assist the upper high class spirit participating in the war, the village sent warriors out toward Strahl, too... Though most of those, including the upper high ranked spirit, never returned. It was said that the heroes appeared toward the final stages of the Divine War, but by then, the upper high class spirit was gone, and many of the warriors from our village had lost their lives...” Ursula continued.

“...So you don’t know any of the specifics, then?” Rio asked inquisitively.

“Indeed — we do not know much about the heroes. The Seven Wise Ones... No, they were already six by that time, so they were what the humans called the Six Wise Gods. Those Six Wise Gods had seemingly appeared from nowhere, and were all equipped with Divine Weapons. That is all we know,” Dominic said contemplatively.

“I have been wondering this for a while, but why do you seem so certain of the existence of a seventh god?” Rio asked. “No one in the Strahl region seems to acknowledge anything like a seventh god.”

“Because our ancestors encountered the one who named themselves the seventh god during the beginning and the end of the Divine War. They visited the village early during the war and requested help from the upper high class spirit of the time to fight. Their goal for visiting the village toward the end of the war wasn’t recorded, but it was noted that they were already exiled from the other six by that time,” Dominic explained.

“...The seventh god didn’t leave any information about the heroes?”

“That I am not sure of, since it was not recorded.”

“Why do you believe those heroes were summoned here from another world, Lord Rio? Even if you say they appeared from outside of this world, I find it hard to believe...” Ursula asked Rio somewhat suspiciously.

“Because I am currently looking after two girls and a boy who used to live in that world.”

Ursula’s eyes widened. “...My word. So those three are the heroes?”

Rio shook his head. “No, they are not — they were in a location irrelevant to the pillars of light. It seemed like they were in the company of two other people just moments before they were summoned here, and they claimed to witness distortions in the air similar to summoning magic. I believe the other two were the ones summoned as the heroes, while the three under my protection were merely dragged along for the ride.”

“Hmm... You were able to communicate with otherworlders?” Syldora asked without a moment’s delay. It was a well-justified question.

“...I was. Or rather, to be more precise, I already knew the language they spoke.”

With a completely serious expression, Rio answered honestly, but vaguely. He wanted to be as truthful as possible to the people he was about to ask a favor from. He already owed the spirit folk so much, and could no longer deceive them this far into their relationship.

“What do you mean by that...?” The elders all looked confused. The only one who understood was Latifa, who was speechless with shock.

“Please forgive me. I doubt my reasons would be believable even if I explained them here, and they are greatly off-topic to the current issue at hand. For now, could I ask that you take what I say at face value and accept that I was able to communicate with them? If necessary, I will explain further at a later date,” Rio said, bowing his head deeply at the elders.

“...I do not mind. I want to hear more about your contract spirit, too.” Ursula seemed to comprehend Rio’s feelings and readily agreed. The other elders exchanged looks before nodding hesitantly.

“All right. Then, is your contract spirit currently with those three people?” Syldora asked, changing the subject.

Rio nodded in acknowledgment. “Yes. Her name is Aishia, and I’m having her stay back in Strahl to protect them,” he replied somewhat apologetically.

“Does Lady Aishia know anything about the summoning of the heroes? Or did you find out anything about her identity?” Syldora asked.

“No, Aishia knew nothing. Not about why she was contracted to me, who she was, or even her own name. The name Aishia was something I gave to her.” Rio shook his head uneasily.

“...I see. Well, that seems fine. A high ranked spirit has awakened; for us, it is an exceedingly auspicious event. Lady Aishia... You named her with the ancient language of us spirit folk, yes? Warm spring, beautiful spring... An appropriate name for this season,” Dominic said, laughing cheerfully.

“Heh. Well, it’s exactly as Dominic says: there’s nothing to be discouraged about, Lord Rio,” Ursula agreed with a gentle smile. The other elders nodded, too, letting a bright atmosphere naturally fall upon the room.

“Thank you very much. Honestly, I pondered quite a bit over whether I should have returned to the village at this point in time. But when it came to Aishia and the other three I’m protecting, I was hoping I could get some information and help from everyone here, so I decided to visit.”

“...While I doubt we will be much help regarding Lady Aishia, it may do you some good to visit the Great Dryas with her. Bring her to the village anytime,” Syldora said with a pensive look.

“However, if I were to bring Aishia to this land, it would become necessary to bring the three under my care along as well...” Rio said, watching Syldora and the others carefully.

“They are your companions, after all. You are free to bring not only Lady Aishia, but the others as well. We will do whatever is in our power to assist you. I’m sure you currently have your hands full with those three, no?” Syldora said, adopting a welcoming attitude toward Miharu and the others.

“...Yes. The three of them wish to seek the other two from whom they were separated from — if they did in fact end up in this world — and return to their own world... but as of right now we’re completely unable to progress. Above all else, I currently have no knowledge about time-space sorcery that can cross worlds. I was hoping that the people here who use time-space sorcery would be able to provide some clues to how they can be returned to their own world.”

“Hmm... To be honest, we also have no idea about time-space sorcery that allows for teleportation across worlds. Of course, we will scrounge through the old texts in our village, but it may be best not to get your hopes up.”

“No, that is more than I could ask for. I had actually feared you wouldn’t allow a complete outsider into the village... I truly do not have enough words to express my gratitude.”

“Hm... With regards to the three, we’ll have to have them agree to a contract of complete confidentiality for when they return to Strahl after having gained knowledge of us. I’m sorry, but the existence of the village cannot be exposed,” Syldora explained.

“Of course. I’ll make sure to explain it to them myself,” Rio agreed reassuringly.

Their stay had been accepted with merely that as a condition — it was not an exceptional request.

“Well, you have watched over them for a while now, and decided to seek help from us on their behalf. I have no concerns with regard to their personalities. There should be no problem,” Ursula offered pleasantly, the corners of her lips turned up in a smile.

“Ursula is right,” Syldora said, followed by the nods of Dominic and the other elders.

“...I am most honored by your faith in me.” Rio bowed his head deeply, his heart filled with emotion. He was, quite simply, so grateful at how he was able to meet such people who believed in him without any doubts in their minds.

“Now that that’s decided, we must prepare to welcome Lady Aishia and the others. We must also inform the Great Dryas of her.” Dominic changed the topic heartily, as though to clear the intimate air that had come between them.

“That’s right. Will you be returning to Strahl immediately, Lord Rio?” Syldora asked, latching onto Dominic’s subject change.

“Yes — I don’t want to keep them waiting for too long. I intend on departing again within a few days.”

“Hm. Then, make sure you stay in the village today, as there’s much more we’d like to discuss about Lady Aishia and the three otherworlders.”

“Of course.”

◇◇◇

Their conversation continued into the afternoon over a light meal. Rio told them various things about Aishia, then decided with the elders what rules would be in place for Miharu, Aki, and Masato’s visit to the village. By the time their discussions had concluded, it had already become evening, so they decided to call it a day.

Rio ended up staying at Ursula’s house that night. After dinner, he was told to rest and relax — which probably meant to look after Latifa.

Rio called her over to the room he was staying in to speak with her alone. Latifa had looked somber ever since the midway point of the discussions, so he needed to explain a few things to her.

“Hey, Latifa. Could you understand the discussion today?” Rio said as he watched her expression. The two of them sat in chairs facing each other.

Latifa nodded uncomfortably. “Yeah, I could. Those people are Japanese people, too, aren’t they?” she asked timidly.

“Yes, they’re Japanese.”

“...Does that mean you told them about how you used to be Japanese, too, Onii-chan?”

Rio nodded with a bitter smile. “That’s right. If I didn’t tell them, they’d wonder about how they were able to communicate with me.”

“Hmph... But it was a secret just between Onii-chan and me.” Latifa pouted her lips somewhat unhappily.

“Are you mad?”

“It’s not that I’m mad, but...”

Rio smiled in faint amusement. “I see.”

“Mgrr! What are you laughing at?”

“At how cute you are, I guess?”

“...That’s not fair, Onii-chan,” Latifa mumbled quietly, giving Rio an admonishing glare.

“What is?”

“Nothing...”

“Listen, Latifa. Just because other people who know about Japan have appeared doesn’t mean that our relationship will change. Isn’t that right?” Rio offered persuadingly with a smile as he watched her sulk.

“...Yeah.”

“Nothing will change how special you are to me.”

“...Yeah.”

“...That’s why I hope you won’t be too shocked by this. Do you remember how I told you about my past life before? About the childhood friend I loved, and the little sister that moved away when my parents divorced.”

“Hm? I remember that...” Latifa inclined her head curiously.

“The truth is, two of the three people I’m looking after right now are those two people.”

“...Huh?”

“Ayase Miharu. The person I always loved when I was Amakawa Haruto. Well, she probably doesn’t remember me anymore... Also, Amakawa — no, Sendo Aki... We only lived together for three years, but she was my little sister. I doubt she remembers anything about me, either. I’m not sure if it’s a coincidence, but they’re two of the three people that are currently in my care,” Rio explained slowly to a confused Latifa.

“...Eh... T-Then, did you t-tell them?! Did you tell those two about yourself?” Not long after Latifa understood the explanation did she start firing back questions in shock.

Rio shook his head calmly. “No, I didn’t tell them I had the memories of someone named Amakawa Haruto. I didn’t think it was the right time to tell them that...” he said in a somewhat troubled voice.

“O-Oh, okay. But... why...?” Latifa asked hoarsely.

“I don’t want to confuse them too much right now — their mental state wouldn’t be the most stable, having suddenly been brought to an unknown world. You used to be the same too, Latifa. Right?” Rio answered with his sound reasoning.

“That’s...” Latifa was at a loss for words. Rio had a point.

However, Latifa didn’t believe that Rio was being honest, despite the fact that he hadn’t lied to her. Was Rio really fine with things that way? She didn’t know.

“That’s why I’d like to ask you to hide your past life from these three people for a while, too. Of course, I won’t forbid you from telling them if you insist on doing so, but... I’d like you to stay absolutely quiet about my past life. Can you promise me that?” Rio asked, showing her a glimpse of the guilt he felt.

“...Onii-chan, you actually want to tell them, don’t you?” Latifa murmured, asking after Rio’s true feelings instead.

“...That’s not true.” Rio shook his head with a bittersweet smile.

“Tell me how you really feel, Onii-chan. Otherwise, I won’t promise you,” Latifa persisted.

“...I want to keep my previous life a secret, just between me and you, I guess,” Rio said with a strained expression, speaking truthfully.

“...That’s unfair. That’s so unfair of you, Onii-chan,” Latifa murmured in a trembling voice, appearing as though she was on the verge of tears; she was unable to decide if Rio was lying or not.

◇◇◇

Two days later, Rio departed from the village once again to make his return trip to the Strahl region. He chose the square before the town hall as his departure point, with Latifa, Sara, Orphia, Alma, Ursula, Syldora, and Dominic there to see him off.

“All right, everyone — I’ll be going now. I should be back in roughly two weeks,” Rio said cheerfully to the seven of them.

“Take care of yourself,” Ursula replied on behalf of the head elders, supported by the nods of the other two.

“We’ll clean up the house where your guests will stay,” Sara said.

“And make the preparations for their welcome,” Orphia added.

Alma chimed in. “I’ll take care of the daily necessities.” The three girls seemed excited to meet the humans that would be coming.

“...Have a safe trip, Onii-chan,” Latifa offered quietly.

“Thanks. I’ll be back soon. Don’t worry — there’s nothing to be scared of.” Rio petted Latifa’s head gently. She stepped forward and buried her face into his chest.

“Hoho, it seems like she’s still at that age where she wants to be doted on,” Ursula mused, watching Latifa with a smile. Naturally, Ursula had also noticed that Latifa was acting strangely after Rio’s discussion with the elders, but she had refrained from intruding, and left the two to solve it amongst themselves. It was how the two of them had always done it, after all.

“She might be worried that her precious big brother will be taken from her by these newcomers. There’s a girl the same age as her, too,” Sara giggled. The others gazed at Latifa.

“...I don’t know what you’re talking about,” Latifa mumbled quietly, tightening her grip around Rio. He made a torn expression as he hugged her, patting her back gently to calm her down. Eventually, her grip loosened.

“Okay. I’m going now, Latifa.” Rio slowly stepped back from Latifa and spoke kindly.

“...Yeah. I’ll be waiting.” Latifa gave a small nod.

◇◇◇

Two weeks later, in a forest on the western outskirts of Amande...

A creepy-looking man in a black robe stood in an area off the road, somewhere no regular citizens would ever pass through.

His name was Reiss.

Surrounding him was a swarm of creatures that had humanoid shapes. Eight had ashen-colored skin and four had skin that was dark to the point of appearing black, each groaning in eerily low tones.

“Fufufu... As expected of the city home to the Ricca Guild — the adventurers working here are all of excellent quality. I’ve obtained some good material thanks to that,” Reiss said to himself proudly as he looked at the grotesque creatures.

“Go, now. Form groups of three and search the forest outskirts of Amande for people that have as much essence as possible. Capture them alive and bring them here. However, make sure to avoid attacking those that have a higher essence than you. Kill as many witnesses as you need to avoid drawing unnecessary attention. I will take care of the western side, so you lot split off into the other directions to search. Your time limit is until sunset tomorrow.”

The strangely-shaped creatures began to move as though they understood Reiss’s words.

“Gruugh.” They formed four groups of two gray-skinned creatures to one dark-skinned leader, then set off at an unbelievably light and fast sprint.

“...Now, once I reach the necessary number of material bodies with this next run, the time will be right. After this last batch, I’ll have to make sure to lie low for a while,” Reiss said with annoyance in his voice, left alone by himself once the figures of the creatures had melted away into the forest. His eyes were completely vacant.

Interlude: Adrift in Another World

Merely an hour before Rio arrived at the grasslands, and just as he discovered the spot where ode and mana had been disrupted by time-space sorcery, three Japanese people dressed in peculiar outfits for this world were standing around in the grass.

“...Miharu?” A middle school girl dressed in her uniform timidly called out to Miharu, who was a high school student that wore her uniform, too.

The girls were unaware of the fact that several pillars of light across the Strahl region had pierced into the heavens less than a minute ago. They had no idea what had happened, nor how they had come to this place.

“Ah, erm... It’s out of range here. M-Maybe it’s broken?” Miharu replied. She had been staring at the “Out of range” display on her phone screen in a daze when she realized her name was called. She put on the best smile she could.

“B-Broken...?” The middle school girl’s expression clouded with worry.

“Did we... warp, or something?” The primary school boy, dressed in his casual clothes, muttered doubtfully in confusion. The modern townscape they were standing in moments ago had changed to a grassy plain before they had realized it.

In a word, it could only be described as “impossible.”

“No way, this isn’t one of those games you always play.” The middle school girl shot him down point-blank.

“Then how would you explain this situation?” the primary school boy objected with a pout.

“I-I don’t know. A-A dream, maybe...”

“That’s not much different than my idea.”

The primary school boy and middle school girl started bickering with each other in somewhat irritated tones, most likely feeling aggressive after being placed in such a bewildering situation.

Miharu took a deep breath and consoled the two children. “Aki-chan, Masato-kun. Let’s calm down and process the situation, okay? Do you two remember where you were before you came here?”

As the eldest, she had to keep herself levelheaded.

“Where we were... Didn’t we all meet up after the opening ceremony at school?” The boy named Masato sighed glumly.

“But weren’t Satsuki-san and Takahisa-kun with us too?” Miharu asked without missing a beat.

“Yeah, they were,” Masato nodded with certainty.

“What about you, Aki-chan?”

Prompted by Miharu, the middle school girl named Aki nodded. “Yeah... We were all together in the residential area.”

“Did the two of you feel anything strange before the landscape changed? Anything you noticed at all. I was talking to Satsuki-san when my vision suddenly looked like it distorted,” Miharu said, explaining the series of events from her own perspective as she questioned the other two.

“...I was talking to my brother when the landscape distorted, I think,” Aki answered with a murmur.

“Now that you mention it, my view also warped...” Masato tilted his head with a hum.

“If the three of us saw the same thing, then it couldn’t be a hallucination... right?” Miharu muttered.

That didn’t change the fact they didn’t know anything about their situation. After all, the peaceful residential area they had been walking through only a short moment ago was now a field of grass, leaving nothing but rocks, hills, and mountains in their view; not a single man-made structure was in sight. In the location they were originally at, a sight like this wasn’t possible no matter how many kilometers they moved.

Thinking about it calmly, the entire situation was so unscientific that it was starting to feel eerie. Perhaps they actually had warped, like Masato said.

An indescribable fear ran through Miharu, making her shudder faintly.

“Hey, did we really warp after all? Is this even Japan anymore?” Masato asked Miharu and Aki, looking suspiciously at their surroundings.

“We have no way of knowing that, since there’s no phone reception out here.” Aki shook her head bluntly.

“L-Let’s make a decision first,” Miharu suggested to the two. “Do we stay here, or do we move?”

The conversation was going around in circles, so she decided to raise her question and change the topic.

“But if we moved, we wouldn’t be able to return here anymore. Someone might come to save us... Are you sure?” Aki asked worriedly.

Despite having no evidence to the contrary, she had the vague belief that they could suddenly be returned back to where they came from if they remained here. Her reasoning to stay put and wait for rescue during times of disaster wasn’t entirely wrong, either; there was a higher possibility of being saved by preserving their stamina, rather than walking around blindly and using up energy.

However, that would increase the possibility of rescue only when they had the supplies for an extended stay — for example, when climbing a mountain, you would inform someone of what day you plan on returning in advance.

“There’s no guarantee anyone will come save us. There aren’t even any roads here. Does anyone even know that we’re here?” The questions Masato was asking were indeed of sound reasoning.

“That’s... true, but...” Aki said, pressured into agreeing.

“Even if we stay here, there aren’t any walls or a roof to shelter us. It’s kind of cold, we have nothing to protect us from the rain, and we barely have any food or water...” Miharu noted, listing all of the disadvantages of remaining where they were. The more she spoke, the more despair she felt for their situation.

“I don’t have any food or water.”

“Me neither...”

Masato and Aki both paled at once.

“I-I have some tea and biscuits. It’ll be fine!” Miharu hurriedly opened her schoolbag, taking out the bottle of tea and the homemade biscuits. She showed them to the other two with cheery encouragement. However, the amount wasn’t enough to ease their concerns.

With such limited supplies, even if I gave it all to the two of them, we’d run out of food and water in no time... I have to do something before that happens. While she somehow managed to calmly analyze the situation, impatience was slowly rising within Miharu.

“Hey, let’s try to find someone. If we stay here, we’ll either starve to death or freeze to death,” Masato proposed anxiously. Seeing Miharu’s composure had helped him keep his own cool, but he could still keenly feel the precariousness of their current situation.

“What do you think, Aki-chan?” Miharu asked.

“Y-Yeah. I agree... But which way should we go?” Aki nodded hesitantly, looking around the grassland with a worried expression. Miharu didn’t know the answer to that either.

“Let’s try heading that way, since the other side has mountains in the distance.” Miharu stifled her worries and pointed south.

◇◇◇

Once they decided the direction in which to proceed, the three of them started to silently move. They walked for about ten to twenty minutes, but there was still no sign of anything man-made. On the contrary, there wasn’t even a single sign of life.

The air was chilly and dry; simply walking parched their throats. After walking for an hour, Miharu made the other two take one sip each of the tea in her bottle. Since this was all the water they had, they needed to ration it economically, but regularly. After all, it was important to keep hydrated when moving.

If only there was a river or something... Miharu thought earnestly as she led the other two, who followed her without complaint.

“...Ah, it’s a person... —Hey, isn’t that a person?!” Masato suddenly said.

“Huh? ...Y-You’re right! It’s a person, a person! Miharu!” Aki’s voice bounced happily.

Far in the distance where Aki and Masato were looking were human-like figures. While they couldn’t tell how far away they were, it looked like a large group of people moving in a line. Upon further inspection, creatures that looked like horses were pulling something among them.

That’s a horse... right? The inconsistency of the sight with the time period made Miharu pause in shock.

“Hey, Miharu! Aren’t we going?! There are people there!” Aki pulled on Miharu’s sleeve.

“Y-Yeah. That’s... right,” Miharu nodded slowly, all while wondering with unease as to where in the world they really were. But it wasn’t just unease in her heart, though — there was faint caution, too.

“Heeey!” Unaware of how Miharu was feeling in her heart, Masato yelled loudly and drew attention to their position.

“Heeey!” Aki followed after Masato.

“Heeey!” Masato and Aki’s voices eventually overlapped with each other. There were people there; placed in a completely unknown situation, the mental relief that fact brought to the two was immeasurably huge.

The two children waved their arms desperately in an appeal as they shouted. Then, having noticed Masato and Aki, several figures left the line at the other end. There were three of them, and they approached Miharu and the others at an oddly fast pace.

Masato and Aki noticed that fact and waved their arms happily.

“...Huh, a horse?”

They soon froze, because they had noticed the figures closing in were on horseback. As Masato and Aki were frozen, the mounted figures came right up to them.

“**** **!” The man riding at the front shouted. The three Japanese students couldn’t understand what he was saying at all.

“***, ****!”

When the leader-like man riding first yelled, the other two came to a halt at once.

The men riding on horseback all had rough facial features, and were clearly not Japanese. They were dressed in light leather armor with dreadfully solid metal swords that were sheathed at their waists.

The men calmed the horses they had just halted and glared down at the three. Aki and Masato backed away in fear.

Miharu was also fearful, but she stood in front of Aki and Masato to protect them.

“Ah, umm... D-Do you understand Japanese?” She opened her mouth to try and say something, then blurted out the first question that came to mind with a trembling voice.

“****’* ****, *** ***?” The apparent leader cocked his head suspiciously.

“Do you know where we are? We seem to be lost...” Miharu asked in English next, refusing to give up.

“*****.” The man shook his head as though he was giving up on communicating.

“Huh? English is no good, too? Then, umm, what should we do... M-Maybe my pronunciation was bad.”

Unable to come to a mutual understanding, Miharu finally faltered, and her unease continued to increase. She was overwhelmed by the unpleasant throbs in her chest.

Behind Miharu, Aki and Masato had completely shrunken in on themselves in silence. They had never spoken to any foreigners in their lives, so they were frightened.

It was understandable — the other party was equipped with swords, after all.

“****, ***’* *** ***** **** *** ** ****? **** ** **** **** *** ****.” One of the men on horseback stared at Miharu’s face and body with a grin as he said something to the leader. There was no restraint in his gaze, making Miharu fidget slightly.

“****, ***’** *****,” the leader replied to the man with a grin on his mouth. His gaze was also fixed on Miharu.

“*** ***** *** ****’* ** *** ******. *** *****, *** ***** ***** ****.” The third man also said something, his line of sight on Aki and Masato as they stood behind Miharu.

“W-What?”

“Hey, isn’t this kind of bad?” Aki and Masato said as they looked up worriedly at the men holding their conversation between themselves.

“*** *****, *** ****.” The man who appeared to be the leader said something, and the other men immediately dismounted from their horses. They all started casually walking toward Miharu, Aki, and Masato.

Miharu spread her arms before Aki and Masato to protect them, placing herself in the line of fire. Like Masato had said, she had a bad feeling about this... but, really, she knew it was already too late.

The three of them slowly backed away.

“D-Don’t come any closer!” Aki suddenly yelled from behind Miharu. Her voice trembled, most likely from fear.

She glared at the men threateningly, but it was like staring down the barrel of a gun.

One of the approaching men burst into cackles at the sight of Aki’s bluff. Then, the leader suddenly drew his sword from the sheath at his waist. No matter how they looked at it, that gleam and thickness of the blade couldn’t have been a fake.

“***’* ****!” The leader-like man suddenly yelled at Miharu, Aki, and Masato.

Aki gave a small shriek. “Eek!”

Masato flinched, too. A bad feeling gnawed away at Miharu bit by bit, paralyzing her legs. It was as though someone had a fist clenched around her heart.

“L-Let’s run! Quickly!” Masato said.

“Y-Yeah!” Aki nodded vigorously.

“Don’t run, you two!” Miharu returned to her senses with a gasp and grabbed Aki’s and Masato’s hands in a fluster.

The men had weapons and were on horseback; she highly doubted they would be able to run from people like that, and running might urge them to kill instead.

More importantly, the air around the men felt abnormal.

“Eh? Ah, but...” Aki tried to say something, but trailed off.

“Don’t run. You don’t know what they’ll do, so obey them quietly. Please?” Miharu muttered, raising their grasped hands to appeal her willingness to go along without resistance. Both of her hands were trembling with fear.

“****.” The leader snorted mockingly at Miharu and the others’ lack of resistance, then gave some kind of order to the other two men from horseback. The two men suddenly moved to obey him, tying Aki and Masato’s hands with rope. They collected the schoolbags the two of them carried, and brought the two children over to the horses, attaching the ropes to the saddles.

Aki and Masato were upset, but quietly obeyed them as Miharu had told them to. The two of them anxiously watched Miharu, who was the only one left behind.

Then, one man stood by Aki and Masato to watch them as the other man approached Miharu. The man looked at her with perverted eyes and let out a jovial whistle, then reached for Miharu’s body with a lecherous movement, when —

“****! *** ****, *** ****!” The leader yelled angrily, making the man retract his hand in a hurry. With a click of his tongue, he snatched Miharu’s schoolbag and tied her hands in an impersonal manner.

Miharu froze as her body shook with an indescribable fear. The thudding in her heart didn’t cease, but when she made eye contact with a worried Aki and Masato, she forced a smile onto her face. Then, Miharu was dragged to the horses and tied to the saddle just like Aki and Masato.

...Was this the right choice? Miharu thought as she saw the despair in Aki and Masato’s expressions.

If Aki and Masato had tried to run earlier, the men might have killed one of them, and that was something she couldn’t allow. While being alive didn’t mean having hope, dying was most certainly the end.

“**** ***!” The leader gave a new order, and the men swiftly mounted their horses.

Miharu and the others were pulled along by the rope attached to the horse saddles and taken to the main party the men belonged to.

◇◇◇

Miharu and the others were taken to a run-down road that was clearly not maintained. On it were over ten wagons with horses that formed a line of two rows; they were surrounded by armed men who were protecting their contents.

Most of the wagons had their covers rolled up, exposing their interior platform to the open. However, the framework was made of a metal as sturdy as a jail cell, and inside were countless numbers of people in raggedy clothes.

For Miharu and the other two, who were raised in modern society, it was clear at this point that this was a different world. They could see the clear division of worlds between the imposingly armed men surrounding the wagon and the lifeless people inside the wagon. Miharu, Aki, and Masato could practically feel and see the bizarre aura hanging in the air about the group.

When the men — those who had broken off from the group to retrieve Miharu and the other two — returned, all the attention turned to them. The three were clearly wearing outfits that were out of place, drawing suspicious looks from the men. However, once the attention on their odd clothing died down, the men’s gazes were gradually drawn to Miharu’s appearance.

With her outfit and physical features (like her hair color, for instance), it was clear to the men that she was a foreigner. Her face was cute, with beautifully refined features, and her feminine body was truly charming — she was slender, but well-balanced. From her soft aura that managed to be both graceful and meek, her upbringing seemed to be on par with the nobility of this world.

A deceivingly gentle wind blew, ruffling both her checker-pleated skirt and glossy black hair that extended down her back. The men’s eyes widened at the sight.

Miharu could keenly feel the presumptuous gazes glued to her, and she stirred uncomfortably, averting her eyes.

“****?” A well-dressed man who had appeared from nowhere addressed the men who had taken the youngsters with a question. His eyes landed on their bindings and narrowed sharply.

“**********. ******, ****, *******? ********.” The leader looked at the three as he said something boastfully to the well-dressed man, then showed him the schoolbags that they’d been carrying.

“**, *******.” The well-dressed man took the schoolbags and inspected them, before voicing an impressed grunt.

He looked at the three of them, and with a gloating grin, he approached them with an appraising look in his eye. He examined their clothes fixedly from point-blank range, touching each of the fabrics and widening his eyes at the quality.

Next, the man set his eyes on the group, before he moved right before Miharu. When he saw her fearful face, a sadistic smile flashed across his own. “****, ******?” he asked, but Miharu couldn’t understand his words and only tilted her head timidly. In response, the well-dressed man put on a vulgar smile.

“*******. **********.” He pointed at Miharu, and jerked his chin at the men around him to follow his order; they jumped to respond promptly.

They pulled Miharu’s bound hands by the rope, leading her away. The wagon she was led to was of better quality than the others, having a proper cover that could serve as shelter from the elements.

Unable to bear the sight of Miharu being dragged away, Aki screamed. “Miharu, wait!”

“Aki-chan, I’ll be fine. You too, Masato-kun... Kya?!”

Miharu had turned around while being led away to smile at Aki and Masato, but the rope was violently yanked, making her lose her balance and nearly trip.

“Miharu!” Aki shouted in a panic.

“Kya?!”

“Whoa!!”

A sharp cracking sound echoed forth, making Aki and Masato shrink in on themselves. The source of the sound was from a whip, which the well-dressed man was controlling skilfully with his overweight body. He continued to swing the whip as a threat toward Aki and Masato.

“Uhh...” Aki had shriveled up completely.

“****. ** **** ***** *******.” The well-dressed man looked at Aki and Masato’s fearfulness and huffed through his nose with satisfaction, lowering his whip, then giving the men nearby an order.

The armed men stirred into action, this time dragging Aki and Masato to a wagon that was different than the one Miharu had been taken to.

With no other choice, Aki and Masato boarded the wagon; it had its platform exposed, and there were hordes of boys and girls around the age of ten gathered on board.

“M-Miharu... What should we do, Masato? What should we do...” Aki asked Masato. She stood in the wagon and grabbed the metal lattice, extremely upset.

“A-Aki, I know how you’re feeling, but it might be better to stay quiet,” Masato whispered to her, worried about their surroundings.

“What are you talking about...” Aki started to object in a sullen tone when she realized the other children on the wagon were glaring at them. She promptly shut her mouth.

There wasn’t an ounce of energy in their faces, but it was clear that they were admonishing Aki and Masato. Perhaps they wanted to tell them not to make a fuss and anger the guards.

“Let’s just sit down quietly for now. We don’t know what they’ll do if we cause a racket,” Masato whispered in her ear, before reading the situation and sitting down in the wagon. With that, Aki had no choice but to sit down next to Masato and hang her head in gloom.

Not long after that, the wagons that Miharu, Aki, and Masato were on departed. However, in no time at all, an uproar ensued. One of the guards at the side of the wagons pointed off the road and yelled something.

“...What?” Aki murmured, raising her head.

She nervously looked around the outside of the wagon and listened carefully. While she couldn’t understand their words, she figured some kind of disturbance had happened; at the same time, she felt a faint tinge of hope that she could use this chance to escape, despite the fact the door of the wagon was locked.

At that moment, Aki saw a figure approach from the side of the road, just next to the wagon where Miharu was. The figure looked to be a boy in his mid-teens.

“...Huh?”

The boy was dressed in an overcoat that she imagined served as travel gear in this world, but when the boy’s face entered her field of view, Aki gasped. His hair was gray, and he had an extremely refined face, but Aki’s attention wasn’t drawn to him because of that.

She had gasped because he seemed the closest to her — racially — than anyone else she had encountered in this world thus far. If she had to describe it, he looked like he was half-Asian.

The aforementioned boy came up to the wagon and started to say something to the guards. She couldn’t hear what they were saying, but the men were clearly being cautious around him.

Soon after that, the well-dressed man appeared to see what was going on. The boy said something, to which the well-dressed man shook his head bluntly. They seemed to be arguing about something.

The gray-haired boy then briefly cast his eyes over the convoy of wagons, and the well-dressed man looked over at the wagon Aki and Masato were on. He soon looked away again, but his eyes had met with Aki’s for a second.

Did he come here to save us? Aki thought to herself hopefully, a strange uneasiness in her chest. The hope that sprouted in the midst of such a desperate situation might have only been that of pure optimism, but it was growing at an accelerating pace.

Aki was staring at the boy with a yearning gaze when, suddenly, the men around them hurriedly began to lower the cover of the exposed wagons. The cover of the wagon Aki and Masato were on was also lowered.

Why are they hiding us?

Aki felt a strong sense of suspicion. Should she take action and seek help? What if she had misread this situation? Doing so could cause her to face dire consequences later.

Would he even believe her circumstances to begin with? She didn’t know.

However, this could be the turning point in their destiny — the last possible chance for them to be saved. If that was the case, she couldn’t just sit around and wait.

Unable to withstand it any longer, Aki stood up with great vigor. “H-Help us!” she cried out desperately, seeking help from the boy.

The boy’s gaze met Aki’s eyes, and a beat later, the cover of the wagon was lowered before Aki.